Southwest Folklore Center Cassette Recordings Collection, 1975-1995
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Slim Kite recitations, July 7, 1985, Kite, Slim Luther, 1985 July 7; Chino Valley, AZ., 1985; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Information from acquisitions file, "Recorded at Dave and Donna Luckow's house, Chino Valley, AZ., July 19, 1985... Contains four recitations... Interview conducted by James S. Griffith... Contains bawdy and obscene material"... Why humans live to be so old -- The Persian kitty, #2 -- The Buggering of Dan McGrew -- The last longhorn --; SWF 85.21/C.1
- Fiddling contest at Armory Park downtown, 1986; Tucson, AZ., 1986; 1 sound cassette, analog, stereo, vol.1; NOTES: Information from acquisitions file, "Taped by Ray Wyack for City Parks Department... annual Tucson Old Time Fiddle Contest, Armory Park, February 23, 1986"...; SWF 86.2/C.1
- Fiddling contest at Armory Park downtown, 1986; Tucson, AZ., 1986; 1 sound cassette, analog, stereo, vol.2; NOTES: Information from acquisitions file, "Taped by Ray Wyack for City Parks Department...annual Tucson Old Time Fiddle Contest, Armory Park, February 23, 1986"...; SWF 86.2/C.2
- 2nd annual Cowboy Poetry Gathering, 1986:Cowboy music #1, Ohrlin, Glen, Reno, NV., Worldwide Communications, p1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Recorded at Elko, Nevada... Musicians include: Glen Ohrlin; George Shawver; Val Geisler; Slim Kite; Earl Rogers...; SWF 86.4/C.1
- 2nd annual Cowboy Poetry Gathering, 1986: Arizona poets, Knox, Ross, Reno, NV., Worldwide Communications, p1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Recorded at Elko, Nevada... Poets: Ross Knox; Slim Kite; Earl Rogers; Everett Brisendine; Vess Quinlin...; SWF 86.4/C.2
- 2nd annual Cowboy Poetry Gathering, 1986: Cowboy music 2, Carpenter, Ed, Reno, NV., Worldwide Communications, p1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Recorded at Elko, Nevada... Musicians include: Ed Carpenter; Baxter Black; Gene Randels; Swede Miller; Brian Morris; Doug Green; Too Slim; Glenn Ohrlin...; SWF 86.4/C.3
- 2nd annual Cowboy Poetry Gathering, 1986: Nevada poets, Fanning, Ernie, Reno, NV., Worldwide Communications, p1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Recorded at Elko, Nevada... Poets include: Ernie Fanning; Georgie Sicking; Larry Schutte; Waddie Mitchell....; SWF 86.4/C.4
- 2nd annual Cowboy Poetry Gathering, 1986: Cowboy music #3a, Tape 1, Bowman, Don, Reno, NV., Worldwide Communications, p1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Recorded at Elko, Nevada... Musicians include: Don Bowman; Gary McMahan; Chris Le Doux; John Neilson; Justin Bishop...; SWF 86.4/C.5
- 2nd annual Cowboy Poetry Gathering, 1986: Classic cowboy recitations, Hancock, Sunny, Reno, NV., Worldwide Communications, p1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Recorded at Elko, Nevada... Performers include: Sunny Hancock; Melvin Whipple; Slim Kite; Waddie Mitchell; Ray Lashley; Yula Sue Hunting; Ernie Fanning; James S. Griffith...; SWF 86.4/C.6
- White Mountain Orchestra and others, White Mountain Orchestra, Billie Maxwell and Rodeo Trio, [198?]; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From cover: "Recorded for James S. Griffith"...Cassette contents derived from acquisitions file: Gooson quadrille (instrumental by White Mountain Orchestra) -- Leather britches (instrumental by White Mountain Orchestra) -- Billy Venero, parts 1 and 2 (Billie Maxwell) -- The Arizona girl I left behind me (Billie Maxwell) -- The Cowboy's wife -- Where your sweetheart waits for you (Billie Maxwell) -- Haunted hunter (Billie Maxwell) -- Arkansas traveler (Rodeo trio) -- When the work's all done this fall -- Cowboy's lament -- Bury me not on the prairie -- Home on the range --; SWF 86.6/C.1
- Potam looria pahko, Amarillas, Juan, 1986; [Tucson, AZ., Southwest Folklore Center], 1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisition file: "Cassette recorded on one side by Felipe Molina at the Yaqui village of Potam, Sonora, Holy Saturday, March 29, 1986. Recorded during the 'Looria Pahko' (Holy Saturday Fiesta). Coontains deer songs, a few pahkola 'sonim'. Recorded with permission. May be used for listening and study, but may not be reproduced for any sort of commerical distribution. Names of tunes not known. Only known musician is Juan Amarillas, the 'tampalco'"... Date on cassette is March 28, 1986...; SWF 86.7/C.1
- Lalo Guerreo at the musuem of art, Guerreo, Lalo, 1986; [Tucson, AZ., Tucson Festival Society], 1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Recorded at the Fiesta Del Presidio on Sunday, April 13, 1986, by the Tucson Festival Society...; SWF 86.9/C.1
- Mike Enis interview, Enis, Mike, [197?]; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisitions file: "Single cassette tape of interview of Mike Enis (ca. 1976) by James S. Griffith about Mike's involvement with "waila" or Chicken scratch music. Enis' family band, Mike Enis and Company, appeared on Canyon Records' first waila record and pioneered in trips to festivals in the mid-1970's"...; SWF 86.10/C.1
- [Three Corridos], Los Cuartreros de Sonora, 1986; [1986]; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisitions file: "Cassette containing three songs from [Chris] Strachwitz's record collection"... More song information in acquisitions file, 86.19/C.1... El Heroe de Nacozari (composed by Jesus Garcia, performed by Los Cuarteros de Sonora) -- El Guarte (composed by Leonardo Yañez, performed by Los Cuarteros de Sonora) -- Parodía de; charrasqueado (composed by Pachuco, performed by Los Cruceños) --; SWF 86.19/C.1
- The Death of Louie Cañas; San Xavier Mission's Lecture, Chinns, Fr. Celestin and Blacky Ramos, 1984; [December 12, 1984]; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Side one contains a copy of the lecture written and narrated by Father Celestin Chinn which tourists hear at San Xavier Mission... Side two contains a song recording of "The Death of Louie Cañas," by Blacky Ramos, Ricky Wilson, and Jerry Ferrin, miners at Magma Mine, Magma Copper Company, San Manuel, Arizona. Louie Cañas was a miner who was killed in a shaft accident... More information on insert...; SWF 86.24/C.1
- Romaine Loudermilk, Loudermilk, Romaine, 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisitions file: "Tape... of cowboy songs performed by the late Romaine Lowdermilk (sic), pioneer Arizona dude rancher. Lowdermilk recorded (in the 50's?) at Audio-Video Recording Studios in Phoenix [and] left the masters with them. Guests and fans of Lowdermilk's, desiring an LP of his singing would order custom pressings... Lowdermilk is referred to extensively in John I. White's "Get along, little doggies: Songs and songmakers of the American West", University of Illinois Press, 1975"... Jose Carlos' daughter -- Flyin' u twister -- Great grandad --Texas maiden -- Moonshine steer -- Lee's Ferry -- Drinkin' tequilla -- Dyin' cowoby -- Lonely -- The Girl on the strawberry roan -- Cowboy's lament (Streets of Laredo) -- Billy the Kid -- Tenderfoot -- Sweet Naomi -- Lopin' along -- Westrn country -- Gol durn wheel -- Zebra Dunn -- Tyin' knots in the devil's tail -- Jake and Roany -- Dude wrangler -- Border affair -- Ramblers cowboy --; SWF 86.25/C.1
- Interview with Mike Lanton, Lanton, Mike, 1986; Flagstaff, AZ., [1986]; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: From acquisitions file: "Interview by Warren Miller with Mike Lanton, [Northern Arizona] cowboy. (Lanton worked for years for Babbit Bro.'s CO ranch.)"... File includes 1 page xerox of Warren Miller's field notes (11/17/86)... Recitations: High chin Bob (by Badger Clark) -- The Legend of boastful Bill (by Badger Clark) -- The Mustang with wings (by Curley Fletcher) -- Just a thinkin' (by Bruce Kiskaddon) --Collector: Warren Miller; SWF 86.28/C.1
- Easy chairs and saddle sores: Cowboy poetry and songs, Mitchell Waddie, Ross Knox and Earl Rogers, 1986; Prescott AZ., Cowboy Folklore Project of Sharlot Hall Museum, 1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Poetry recorded at KNAU FM, Flagstaff...Earl Rogers's songs were recorded, and tape mastering done at CAVE Studio, Prescott...Yavapai Pete -- Easy chairs and saddle soars -- The Riders -- An Experiment -- Wild Horse Charlie -- The Brewery Gulch Gazette -- The Dude wrangler -- Women drivers -- The Little bull -- The Tenderfoot or the D-Z horse wrangler -- Hollywood bound -- The Little blue roan -- Gettin' put in double harness -- Pegleg pig -- Hook'um cow -- The Flyin' outlaw -- The old nighthawk --; SWF 86.31/C.1
- 3rd annual cowboy poetry gathering, 1987: Arizona poets, Elko, NV., 1987; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Tape of Arizona session at the 3rd annual cowboy poetry gathering, Elko, Nevada, January 29, 1982...Introduction by Warren Miller...Acquisition file includes program from Elko gathering, with photographs...Reciters in order are: Rolf Flake; Vess Quinlan; Everette Brisendine; Ross Knox; Homer Bryant; Jody Sixkiller..; SWF 86.32/C.1
- Interview with Abraham (Abe) R. Loroña, Loroña, Abraham (Abe) R., 1987; Tucson, AZ., Celestino Fernandez' office, University of Arizona, January 14, 1987; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Interview with Abraham Loroña by Celestino Fernandez and James S. Griffith concerning Loroña family traditions, horse races, and "El Corrido del Merino"...Acquisition file includes Mr. Loroña's typed text of "El Merino" and "El Corrido del Palomino," which tells of a race between Oquitoa and Altar. Collector: James S. Griffith and Celestino Fernandez; SWF 87.1/C.1
- Archie Hughes' poems, Hughes, Archie, Green, AZ., 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Poems by Archie Hughes...Acquisition file includes xerox of newspaper article about him...; SWF 87.5/C.1
- Music from the Power House, Goosewings, Timmins, Ontario, The Ojibway and Cree Cultural Center; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Ojibway and Cree Indian music...; SWF 87.6/C.1
- Squaw dance love songs, Rock Point Singers of Arizona: Two step dance and skip dance songs, Rock Point Singers, 1985; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1985; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol.3; NOTES: Photograph on cover of the Rock Point Singers... Singers inlcude: Harry Tso Begay, lead singer; Clarence Woody, drummer; Glen Tsosie; Ralph Dee, Jr.; Adran Begay... Two step dance songs: A Lying Mexican girl -- A Partner wants to go to Gallup -- Hard to be jealous -- My girl got jealous 'cause of my cousin -- Dear sweetheart, let's go dance -- You were my sweetheart a long time ago -- Tuba City girl at Omaha, Nebraska -- Skip dance songs: A Man overlooking his wife -- Dear darlin', I still remember -- My pretty girlfriend -- Are you sure you are mine? -- Even if it happened, I still remember you -- Hello, Honey, you're here -- What happened when I tried to whistle at you? --; SWF 87.14/C.5
- Navajo two-step songs: Chinle Valley Song and Dance Festival, 1986; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records Productions, p1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Separate photographs of each of the seven performing groups on cover...Recorded live, April 1986, at the Chinle Valley Song and Dance Festival...Performers include: Tok-Den-Nas-Shai Singers; T/L Swingers; Smoke Signal Travelers; Four Corners Singers; Nataani Nez Travelers; Beclabito Valley Singers; Chinle Valley Boys...Roughin' it smoothley -- Six-pack to go -- Dulce girl -- Curly-haired girl -- She's a dearest Hopi girl -- Keep track of me -- Do you still remember our old acquaintance? -- My mother dislikes our relationship -- My girlfriend is ignoring me -- My short-term girlfriend -- Apache girl -- Tuba City sweetheart -- Be with me for awhile -- When are we going home --; SWF 87.14/C.6
- Navajo skip dance songs: Chinle Valley Song and Dance Festival, 1986; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records Productions, p1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Separate photographs of each of the seven performing groups on cover...Recorded live, April 19, 1986, during the Chinle Vallely Traditional Song and Dance Festival, Chinle, Arizona...Performers include: Beclabito Valley Singers; T/L Swingers; Smoke Signal Travelers; Nataani Nez Travelers; Four Corners Singers; Tok-Den-Nas-Shai Singers; Chinle Valley Boys...Tell mother we're leaving -- Talk of town girl -- Hey, girl -- Proposing -- Be my sweetheart for one night -- Met me at this song and dance -- Going home -- Oklahoma girl -- Why do you go with married men -- Maiden in buckskin -- Vietnam memories -- Youthful memories -- I'll be there unexpectedly; SWF 87.14/C.7
- Chinle Valley Singers: Navajo two-step dance, skip dance and double time songs, Chinle Valley Singers, 1984; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records Productions, p1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph on cover of the Chinle Valley Singers... Singers include: Elizabeth Davis, lead singer; Elsie Deswood; Anita Davis; Esther Davis; Linda Teller; Geraldine Little... 6 two-step dance songs -- 6 skip dance songs -- 4 double time songs --; SWF 87.14/C.8
- The hearts of Navajoland, Chinle Valley Boys: Navajo two-step and skip dance songs, Chinle Valley Singers, 1986; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records Productions, p1986; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol.2; NOTES: Photograph of Chinle Valley Boys on cover... Singers include: Eddie Jones, lead singer; Bennie Begay; Jimmy Shorty; John Hardy; Gjermundson Yazzie; Harry Yellowhair; Danny Y. Begay; Pat J. Ashley... Little girl -- You'll grow up beautifully -- That girl in Chinle -- China girl from faraway -- Blackfoot girl -- When we're going back -- Youthful memories -- A Girl at intertribal ceremonial -- A Blue eyed girl of Flagstaff -- Girl at Window Rock dance -- I'll be there unexpectedly --; SWF 87.14/C.9
- From the heart of Navajoland, Chinle Valley Boys: Navajo Two Step and Skip Dance Songs, Chinle Valley Boys, 1986; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records Productions, p1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Chinle Valley Boys on cover...Singers include: Eddie Jones, lead singer; Bennie Begay; Jimmy Shorty; John Hardy; Gjer Mundson Yazzie; Henry Yellowhair; Danny Y. Begay; Pat J. Ashley...Be with me for awhile -- My dear sweet heart -- You were my friend long ago -- You comb your hair -- Attend every squaw dance -- Even if you have a boyfriend -- For no reason I missed our date -- Dancing to the Chinle Valley Boys -- Chute #7, Nataani Nez girl -- I'll be there unexpectedly --; SWF 87.14/C.10
- Dennehotso Swinging Wranglers, Navajo two-step and skip dance songs: Swing with the Wranglers, Dennehotso Swinging Wranglers, 1984; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Dennehotso Swinging Wranglers...Performers include: Wesley Gray, drums; Reeder Dee, assistant drums; Johnny Richards, lead singer; Harold Richards, manager; Herbert Featherhat; Dickson Hosknie; Tulley Blackmountain...Biographical information about the group inside cover...Two-step songs: Swing with the Wranglers -- Pretty woman -- Colorado cowgirl -- Pueblo girl -- Dance with your dancing partner -- Avon -- Wondering where you are -- Skip dance songs: Coal miner's daughter from Peabody -- Coca Cola cowboy -- Letter from a friend -- Taste the high country -- Be my one dancing partner -- Secretary from Window Rock --; SWF 87.14/C.11
- Dennehotso Swinging Wrangers: Navajo skip dance songs, Dennehotso Swinging Wranglers, 1984; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol. 2; NOTES: Musicians include: Harold Richards, manager; Johnny Richards, lead singer; Reeder Dee, assistant drummer; Herbert Leatherhat; Tulley Blackmountain; Dickson Hosknie; Wesley Grey, drummer...Skip dance songs: When you finish N.C.C. -- Spanish girl from Reno, Nevada -- Navajo lady in rich Navajoland -- Your grandma doesn't like me -- Come back to me -- He's dancing with my dancing partner -- Skip dance songs: Met a Ute girl in Cortez, Colorado -- Came home with a Blackfoot girl -- Turn me loose, it's party time -- You are always mad -- My dancing partner is here from Winslow, Arizona -- Happy birthday --; SWF 87.14/C.12
- Dennehotso Swinging Wranglers: Navajo two-step dance and skip dance songs, Dennehotso Swinging Wranglers, 1984; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, 1984; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol. 3; NOTES: Musicians include: Harold Richards, manager; Johnny Richards, lead singer; Reeder Dee, assistant drummer; Herbert Featherhat; Tulley Blackmountain; Dickson Hosknie; Wesley Gray, drummer...Two-step dance songs: K-town girl in Wrangler -- Going back with a Comanche girl -- Sugar coated Sioux Indian girl -- Teddy Bear -- Arizona Wranglers' cheerleader -- Going home -- Skip dance songs: She's wearing a crown -- Let's go to the first night -- Chinle barrel racer -- Little Joe the wrangler -- Hey girl, don't be cruel -- Bye bye love --; SWF 87.14/C.13
- Navajo squaw dance songs: Four Corners Singers of Teec Nos Pos, Arizona, Four Corners Singers, 1980; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, 1980; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Four Corners Singers on cover...Recorded June 8, 1980 at Teec Nos Pos, Arizona, by Raymond Boley...Performers include: Woody Johnson; David Jim; Ben Silas; Clarence Weston...Mexican girl -- Paiute girl -- No Fat Valley's daughter -- Blackfoot girl from Idaho -- Girl friends photo -- I remember you by your picture -- Baby with curly hair -- Jambolaya -- Old lady's daughter -- Ute girl --; SWF 87.14/C.14
- Navajo skip dance songs: Four Corners Singers of Teec Nos Pas, Arizona, Four Corners Singers, 1983; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1983; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol. 2; NOTES: Photograph of the Four Corners Singers on cover...Recorded April 2, 1983 in Phoenix, Arizona...Ray Boley, producer...Musicians include: Woody Johnson; David Jim; Clarence Weston; Tom Lowe; Leo Johnson; Robert Gould; Calvin Weston...Leave him alone -- You confused me with your plans -- My girl friend -- You had your arms around her all night -- When my sweetheart arrives -- Tried to go with you when you were single -- Let's cruise to Cortez -- Ute girl wants to dance with me -- Met a girl in Kayenta -- She tried to take me back -- Always remember you -- She drinks and runs around --; SWF 87.14/C.15
- Navajo two-step dance - Love songs: Four Corners Singers of Teec Nos Pos, Arizona, Four Corners Singers, 1983; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, 1983; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Four Corners Singers on cover...Recorded April 2, 1983 in Phoenix, Arizona...Raymond Boley Producer...Performers inlcude: Woody Johnson, David Jim; Clarence Weston; Tom Lowe; Leo Johnson; Robert Gould; Calvin Weston...Six songs -- Six songs --; SWF 87.14/C.16
- Four Corners Singers of Teec Nos Pos, Arizona: Navajo skip dance and two-step dance songs, Four Corners Singers, 1984; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1984; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol.4; NOTES: Photograph of the Four Corners Singers on cover... Musicians include: Woody Johnson, lead singer; Jimmy Cody, lead singer; Tom Lowe, drummer; Leo Johnson; Jackson Cody; Frederick Johnson... Skip dance songs: My one and only -- Love me tonight -- You don't understand, Grandma -- My dream about a girl -- You are the one -- The Shawl dancer -- Two-step dance songs: Forbidden to go among the crowd -- Going back to Idaho with my Shoshone girl -- My old time flame -- T-bird Ute girl -- Respect Grandma -- Dancing girl of Shiprock -- Brainwashing girl --; SWF 87.14/C.17
- Four Corners Singers of Teec Nos Pos, Arizona: Navajo two-step dance and skip dance songs, Four Corners Singers, 1985; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1985; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol.5; NOTES: Photograph of Four Corners Singers on cover... Musicians include: Woody Johnson; David Jim; Tommy Lowe, drummer; Clarence Weston; Leo Johnson; John MacDonald... Navajo two-step dance songs: Take care, my people -- Shiprock sweetheart -- Southern Ute girl in Ignacio -- Wonder where he is -- She tempted me -- You been fooling me -- Navajo skip dance songs: Too many boyfriends -- Chile girl -- Black Mesa girl -- Waiting for dance --; SWF 87.14/C.18
- Belclabito Valley Singers: Navajo two-step dance songs, Belclabito Valley Singers, 1986; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, 1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of the Belclabito Valley Singers... Singers include: Daniel Van Lee, manager; Willie Lee, singer; John Blue Eyes, drummer; Henry Yabeny; Francis Morgan; Paul C. Benally; Dave Johnson; Harry Harrison; Jessie Smith; Rosemary Lee; May Lee; Helen Toglena... Skip dance songs: Tuba City sweetheart -- Leaving my sweetheart -- Take you back to homeland -- Lady's daughter -- Very persuading -- What about me -- Behave -- Two-step dance songs: Secretary form Navajo, N.M. -- Herd the goats on sight -- Future daughter-in-law -- Beautiful curly hair girl -- Hopi man from Oraibi -- Boozing Grandpa --; SWF 87.14/C.19
- Beclabito Valley Singers: Navajo skip and two-step dance songs, Belclabito Valley Singers, 1986; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1986; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of Beclabito Valley Singers on cover... Singers include: Daniel Van Lee, manager; Willie Lee, lead singer; John Blue Eyes, drummer; Henry Yabeny; Francis Morgan; Paul C. Benally; Dave Johnson; Harry Harrison; Jessie Smith; Rosemary Lee; May Lee; Helen Toglena... Skip dance songs: Fraulein -- Love you truly -- Sweet Georgia Red -- Remembering Apache girl -- Mexican Senorita -- Love Letter -- Two step dance songs: BVS grand entry song -- T.O.T. girl -- She's so fine -- Where's the beef -- Memory of June, July -- Mom's approval -- We'll go steady --; SWF 87.14/C.20
- Bita Hochee Travelers: Navajo vol.2, Bita Hochee Travelers, 1978; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1978; 1 sound cassette, analog; Notes: Photograph on cover of Bita Hochee Travelers... Musicians include: Ned B. Morris; Lee Begay; Sam Begay; Larry Gishie... Oh, why of all this -- First night across deep canyon -- It's all your fault -- Fat little Mexican boy -- Big rumor -- Old sweetheart -- Sweetheart made in Japan -- Diamond ring -- Window Rock secretary -- Good rug weaver -- Happy birthday -- Ft. Defiance Agency queen --; SWF 87.14/C.21
- Bita Hochee Travelers (Navajo, Arizona): Modern skip dance songs and modern two step dance songs, vol.3, Bita Hochee Travelers, 1980; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1980; 1 sound cassette, analog; NOTES: Photograph of the Bita Hochee Travelers on cover... Musicians include: Ned Morris; Lee Begay; Ned Morris, Jr.; Gilbert Begay; Lee Begay, Jr... I gave you all my money -- Why crawling in the bush at Sage Brush -- Hangover in Mexico -- I can't believe what was happening -- Follow a cousin -- Cut out -- Commotion of Big Mountain -- Get away Chevrolet -- Chicago bicyclist -- Nashville, Tennessee -- Pretty Hopi girl -- Model T. Ford --; SWF 87.14/C.22
- Navajo two step dance songs, Bita Hochee Travelers, 1985; Phoenix, AZ., Canyon Records, p1985; 1 sound cassette, analog, vol.4; NOTES: Photograph on cover of the Bita Hochee Travelers... Musicians include: Ned Morris; Lee Begay; Ned Morris, Jr.; Gilbert Begay; Lee Begay, Jr... Traveler's warm up song -- I gave up on you when I was single -- Oh, my amigo -- Jealous Grandma -- Avon lady -- Navajo country cowboy -- Rodeo queen -- Baby, Daddy's coming home -- Hitchhiking back to Kansas City -- The Long walk -- I can't travel with my prettiest sweetheart -- I'm your in-law --; SWF 87.14/C.23